本字幕由 PTT同志影视作品板 2013重新校稿
原字幕取自网路资源  仅供学习 禁用任何商业盈利行为
校稿：Finn、Aaa、mohiwa
同志亦凡人 Queer As Folk S01E13
太保守了
Too conservative.
布莱恩
Brian!
好吧  同事们
Okay, boys.
给你们15分钟
You've got 15 minutes.
说说你们的方案吧
What've you got for me?
舒尔曼鞋的设计
The Schulmann shoe layout.
你绝对会爱死它的
You're going to love it.
爱不爱由我说了算
I'll be the judge of that.
打扰一下
Sorry.
你来找人的吗
You looking for someone?
是啊  舒尔曼鞋的会议
Yeah. The Schulmann shoe meeting.
莱德先生说我应该出席的
Mr. Ryder said I should sit in,
过来学点东西
Learn a thing or two, he said.
布莱恩可是最棒的
Well, Brian is the best.
最棒的
The best.
谢了  布莱德
Thanks, Brad.
恩...我是鲍勃
Uh, I-I'm Bob.
我才是布莱德
I'm Brad.
我是基普·汤玛斯
I'm Kip Thomas.
我还是个新人
I just started here.
那好  坐下吧  基普·汤玛斯
Well, sit your ass down, Kip Thomas.
这两位同事正准备露一手
The boys are about to put on a show.
那麽...
So...
这麽丑的鞋  我们要怎麽让它变成有市场呢
How do we make this fucking ugly shoe exciting?
跟去年五月的那件
The same way we made those fucking ugly raincoats
-丑雨衣一样　　　　　-模特儿
-Exciting last May.  -Models.
把目光从鞋子本身
By taking your eye off this shoe...
转移到模特儿脸上
And putting it on this face.
是啊  问题是我们要卖的不是这张脸
Yeah, but t-the trouble is that we're not selling this face.
我们卖的是这双恶心巴拉的鞋
We're selling this hideous shoe.
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
我蛮喜欢的  这...
Uh, I like it. It's, um...
这方案挺不错的
It's really good.
不过...
Only...
-不过？  -不过？
-Only?　 -Only?
为什麽要把商品藏起来呢
Well, why try and hide what the product is?
接着说
Go on.
我会拍一张鞋的照片
I'd just photograph the shoe.
恩...放一个旁白框在旁边
With maybe a... a thought bubble
说着  像是...
Saying some- thing like, uh...
「吾非时尚」
"I'm not hip...
我乃经典！」
I'm a classic."
布莱恩  请问我们能继续了吗
Brian, may we continue, please?
不  你们不用继续了
No, you may not.
「吾非时尚  我乃经典！」
"I'm not hip, I'm a classic."
你赋予它一种个性
You've given it personality,
带着幽默  还包含了一种高贵质感
With humour, and retained its so- called dignity.
你来这儿多久了
How long have you been here?
2个月
Uh, two months.
知道吗  他们在这里工作两年了
You know, they've been working here for two years.
去起草方案吧
Draw it up.
我?
Me?
-他?   -他?
-Him?  -Him?
恩
Him.
他们俩会帮你的
The boys'll help you out.
是不是啊  孩子们
Won't you, boys?
知道吗  我得说在一年之前
You know, I just have to say that a year ago
我们从没想过  我们会有
I don't think any of us would have dreamed that we'd be...
怀孕的一天  我是说
Sitting here pregnant. I mean, it's...
真难以置信
Really happened.
感谢那两个勇敢的开创先锋
Thanks to two true trail-blazing pioneers,
茉蕾妮和琳赛
Melanie and Lindsay.
你们现在可是榜样了
Now you're role models.
我们所有人的榜样  谢谢你们
For us all. thank you.
真希望她们赶紧走人
I wish they'd all leave.
嘘  别让他们听见啦
Shh, you don't want them to hear you.
听见就听见阿  我们干嘛要忍受这些啊
I don't care if they do. Why did we go through with this?
我们都计划了好几个月了
We planned it for months.
我们不能让弗兰妮和佐伊失望
We couldn't disappoint Franny and Zoe,
不然她们会怎麽想
How would they feel?
那你觉得我会怎麽想
How do you think I feel?
我自己就像个愚蠢的大骗子
Like a liar and a fool.
我们能不能晚点再谈这个
Can we talk about this later?
当然了亲爱的  像其他事儿一样拖着
Sure, honey, like every- thing else.
我要来去喝点酒了
I'm going to go spike the punch.
太可爱了
Oh, it's so cute.
弗兰妮真是小巧又可爱
Franny's so cute and tiny.
老天  我讨厌这种人
Christ, I hate cute and tiny.
老天啊
Oh, god.
你应该是她最好的朋友
You're probably her best friend.
从高中起就是了
Since high school.
哦 干
Oh, fuck.
十分赞同你的意见
I'll drink to that.
别担心
Don't worry anyways,
我也讨厌小巧又可爱的那些鬼话
I hate cute and tiny, too.
婴儿皮外套!!
Baby leather jacket, ah!
实在太可爱了
That is so adorable!
老天啊  我现在
Oh, Christ, I would just kill
真想去抽支烟
For a cigarette right about now.
这些宝宝之类的事情快把我逼疯了
All this baby business is just making me a little crazy.
为什麽 是因为你想要个孩子吗
Why, because you want one?
是不想要个孩子
Because I don't want one.
别误会  我挺喜欢小孩子的
Don't get me wrong, I like kids.
只不过是别人家的孩子
Other people's kids.
估计也就喜欢10分钟吧
For about 10 minutes.
我算是个工作狂的Ｔ婆
I'm more of a career dyke myself.
我过去也常常这麽说
I used to say the same thing.
直到我们有了自己的儿子
That was until we had our son.
我是茉蕾妮·马库斯
I'm Melanie Marcus.
是  我知道  「榜样」嘛
Yeah, I know. the role model.
我是玛丽安·麦克唐纳
I'm Marianne Macdonald.
绝对不是个榜样
Definitely not a role model.
那真不错
Well, good for you.
不过  我想你可以叫我"PC"
Though, I suppose you could say I am "pc".
前提是  "PC"的意思是
That is, if "pc" stands for...
舔阴唇的女人
"Performs Cunnilingus".
老天  你真是个怪人
Oh, god, you're wicked.
谢谢
Thank you.
那麽...
So...
想跟我溜出去抽支烟吗
You want to sneak outside for a smoke with me?
P-town的狂欢派对就要到了  伙计们
P-town party's coming up, boys.
跟之前一样 我会去订位的
I'll make the reservations, as usual.
三个位子
For the three of us.
三个人？
Three of us?
是啊  我  艾美特  还有泰德
Yeah, me and Emmett and Ted.
我们需要长辈一旁监督着
Oh, we need someone older to chaperone.
真是太有才了  我崇拜你的机智反应啊
What sparkling wit. I live for your repartee.
那我呢
And what about me?
-你可不能去 　　 -为什麽
-You can't go. 　-Why not?
你可是交往中
You're in a relationship.
还是说你忘了自已有家室？
Or have you forgotten?
风花雪月与你无缘喽
No more fun for yo-ou.
大卫说我可以去
Oh. David said I could go,
只是我要乖乖的而已
As long as I behave myself.
那还去干嘛？
Well then, what's the point of going?
表示我和小艾多一点机会了
Just means more men for me and Em.
是不是  小艾
Right, Em?
哈
Huh?
是啊　　是啊
Oh, yeah, yeah.
你是怎麽了?
What's the matter with you?
刮毛不小心…　蛋疼吧
He's got razor-burn on his balls.
我没事
I'm fine.
我很好
那就滚去舞池跳舞
Well then get your ass on the dance floor.
你来吗  还是说我们得把你抬过去
You're coming? Or do we have to carry you?
我想先喝完这瓶再说
I just, uh, I-I just want to finish my drink.
你好  我是艾美特
H-hi, it's Emmett.
救命啊
Help!
他们要去p-town的狂欢派对
They're making plans to go to p-town.
我  我想去
And I-I... want to go.
那些男人
Uh, all those men...
还有嗨药
All those drugs.
抱歉
Sorry.
这还不是最糟的
And that's not the worst of it.
今天我差点卖了我祖父临终之前
Today I almost sold the watch my grandfather gave me
留给我的手表
on his deathbed...
就为了买
to buy a ticket for...
芭芭拉那场所谓的
Barbra's absolutely
「最终告别　我发誓－这真的是最後」
Final farewell, I-swear-to-god-
「告别演唱会的门票」
This-is-it concert. I mean,
这周的薪水几乎都养不活我自己了
I can barely survive on my week's salary
我还去帮着填饱布连小姐的荷包？
and I-I'm going to help fill Mrs. Brolin's coffer?
悲剧
Sick.
我生病了
I'm sick.
但你还有救
But there's a cure.
所以你才会去了"看见希望"的聚会
That's why you came to "See The Light".
相信我  我理解你的感受
Believe me, I know how you feel.
我是过来人
I've been there.
你看
Look at this.
这是谁
What do you see?
某个变装皇后
A picture of a drag queen.
要不就是你妈妈
Or your mother.
这是我
That was me.
不会吧
No-o-o! Come on!
但你现在这麽...
But you're so...
直男外表?  谢谢
Straight? Thank you.
我保留这张照片  把它当作过去生活的回忆
I keep this photo as a reminder of my former life.
但即使这样  我也知道在这些假发
But even then, I knew under all those wigs
和美丽的长裙下
and those fabulous gowns,
隐藏着一个渴望自由的
there was a conservative,
保守共和党电脑分析师
republican computer analyst dying to be free.
这就是"看见光明"对我的帮助
That's what "See The Light" did for me.
你也会得到同样的帮助
And it can do the same for you,
-如果你是认真想改的话  　-我是
-If you're serious.      -I am.
我是认真的  我发誓
I am serious. I swear to god.
很好  但别自欺欺人
Good. But don't fool yourself.
这过程不会简单
It won't be easy.
有时你可能必须
At some point you may even have to
让自己远离
extricate yourself from...
某些让人堕落的影响
certain corrupt influences.
你是说我的朋友们吗
You mean my friends?
如果他们让你堕落
Are they really your friends
那还叫朋友吗
If they lead you into temptation?
他们绝不是故意的
Well, they never do it deliberately.
艾美特  如果你要走向光明
Emmett, if you see the light
不能让任何人或事
You mustn't allow anything or anyone
使你越走越偏离正轨
to divert you from the path.
谢谢你对我的支持  马特
Thank you, Matt, for your support.
这是我的职责所在
Hey, that's why I'm here,
确保你不会走歪路
To make sure you don't slip.
布莱恩
Brian.
你已经当了执行长吗
You CEO of the company yet?
那得再给我几周时间
Ah, give me a week or two.
莱德先生告诉我
So, Mr. Ryder told me
你真的把我的创意用在鞋子广告里
You're really going to use my ideas for the shoe ads.
我会窃其精华  再改成我的名字
I'll steal anything good and put my name on it.
很好
That's great.
但鲍勃和布莱德不太高兴
Although Bob and Brad aren't too happy about it.
没才华的人才会不高兴
Well, people with no talent usually aren't
特别是看到有真才实学的人出现
when someone with real talent comes along.
我听说你自己就才华出众
Yeah, I hear you're pretty talented yourself.
事实上 其实你还声名在外
In fact, you have a reputation.
是吗
I do?
替公司拉拢不少大客户
For being the best account exec in the company.
是的  包括这一点
Yeah. That too.
这也是我拜托高层让我跟你工作的原因
And that's why I asked if I could work with you.
我以为是莱德叫你过来的
I thought Ryder assigned you.
我...
Yeah. I, uh...
骗你的
lied.
过来  给你看样东西
Come here for a second, I want to show you something.
这是我们为"自由空气"公司做的竞标广告
This is a new campaign we're starting for Liberty Air.
你就去这个团队吧
I want you on the team.
天啊  太好了
Oh, my god. That's... th-that's... fantastic!
我真不知道该如何感谢你
How can I ever thank you?
做好工作就行了
By doing a good job.
你尽管放心
You can count on it.
我还想告诉你…
I just want you to know that you can...
我随时听候你差遣
You can count on me for anything.
不论是白天还是晚上..
Day or night.
你真的是要飞黄腾达了
Well, you really are going for the gold watch.
我说真的
I mean it.
因为我觉得你真的...
Because I think you're really...
很性感
really amazing.
你这是做什麽
What are you doing?
妈的
Shit.
抱歉　嗯..
I'm sorry, um...
我不是故意..
I didn't mean to, uh...
我不知道刚才在想什麽
Look, I don't know what I was thinking.
无论如何你在想什麽
Yeah, well... whatever it was,
你都想错了
You thought wrong.
因为  我才是那个
Because... I'm the one...
采取主动的人
who makes the first move.
你居然在办公室干了他？
You fucked him in your office?
这麽多年来 他是放我桌上
He was the best thing to
最好的东西了
come across my desk in a long time.
你简直难以置信
You're unbelievable.
他也这麽说的
Yeah, that's what he said.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean it like that.
别跟我说 你的大Q超市就没人乱搞过
Don't tell me, no one's ever had a big O" at the Big Q.
-我可不清楚　　　　   -我可清楚的得 第一手消息
-I wouldn't know. 　　-Well, I would. From first-hand.
我的意思是「第一手消息」
And I mean, "first-hand" experience.
难道你...
Are you saying...
记得去年圣诞我去接你
You remember last Christmas when I came to pick you up
你正忙着布置圣诞节饰品?
And you were setting up for Santa's workshop?
别是圣诞老人
Not Santa,
千万别说你干过圣诞老公公
don't tell me you fucked Santa!
即使是我  也不会做这种事的
Ah, even I wouldn't do that.
我对胖子不感兴趣
I'm not into fat.
是他的小精灵
His Elf.
不会吧
You didn't!
他的个子都长在另一个地方了
What he lacked in feet he made up for in inches.
我不想听下去了
I don't want to know.
但你最好小心
But you better be careful.
在办公室做
I mean, doing it in your office may be
就算是你  也有些太冒险
A little too high-risk, even for you.
是他自己送上门来的
But he asked for it, he came on to me.
我送他一个上好的机会
I gave him a great opportunity,
和一次上好的性交
And a great fuck.
他可没得抱怨
He has no complaints.
我们的荣幸  弗兰妮
Well, it was our pleasure, Franny.
我们也很愉快
Yeah, we had fun too.
随便哪天都有可能
So, I guess it's any day now.
别担心  到时我们会去的
Well when it happens, don't worry. We'll be there, okay?
向佐伊问好
Love to Zoe.
茉蕾也向你们问好
And Mel sends her love too.
好  再见
Okay. Bye!
-弗兰妮和佐伊向你问好　　　　　　  -那敢情好
-Franny and Zoe send their love.　 -That's nice.
她们真的很感谢我们参加送礼会
They really appreciated the shower
而且很喜欢我给婴儿床做的玩具
And they really liked the mobile I made for over the crib.
你一直这麽激动累不累啊
Don't you ever get tired of being cheery?
才不会累呢
You have no idea.
我累了  这些事占用我这麽多时间
Well, I'm tired. I'm tired of putting in these extra hours
好让你可以照顾宝宝去吧  所以你何不就
So you can be with the baby, so why don't you just go,
-看宝宝去          -这不是我一个人的事
-Be with the baby? -It's not just for me.
我希望你别这样说了  盖斯可以
I wish you'd stop saying that. It's so Gus...
由他的妈妈们  而不是由陌生人抚养
Can be raised by one of his mommies instead of a stranger.
现在你可以去照看他了
Now can I please just get back to work?
你先为你的行为道歉之後
Not until you apologize for the way
我再去
You behaved at the shower.
我的什麽行为？
How did I behave?
你太无礼了
You were rude.
主要是你有一半时间都心不在焉
Critical, half the time you weren't even there.
那你的行为呢？　假笑得散发光芒呢
What about your behaviour? Smiling and gracious as ever,
好像我们真的没问题一样
As if nothing's wrong.
问题是很多
Oh, plenty is wrong.
但不用让朋友都知道吧
We just don't have to share it with our friends.
也许她们应该知道
Well, maybe we should.
她们也许该知道她们眼中的榜样
Maybe our friends should know that their role models
其实不完美
Aren't so perfect after all.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去抽烟
For a smoke.
《抢救雷恩大屌》《心灵捕屌》
"Shaving Ryan's Privates", "Good Dick Hunting",
《天下最大屌》
"As Big As It Gets".
确实很大
It did get big.
掰掰!
Gone!
《第六根追缉令》...经典电影
Oh, "Fatal Erection", film classic.
我觉得这没什麽影响
I don't suppose it would do any harm to...
算了  掰
No. Gone.
纯银屌环
Sterling silver cock ring.
戴着很漂亮
Looked fabulous on.
但总是要抛光
But it did require a lot of polishing, so...
不要了
Gone!
艾美
Hi, Em!
你们好
Oh, hi.
我来拿我的信件
I just came by to get the mail.
都在那儿
Ah, it's right there.
你想不想去吃个..
And wanted to see if you wanted to grab a bite to...
你在做什麽
What're you doing?
春季大扫除
Spring cleaning.
可现在是12月
It's December.
只是捐些东西给游民
Yeah, I'm just... I'm donating some things to the homeless
看看
So...
黑皮裤  G片
Black leather chaps, porn tapes,
还有双头龙
And a double-headed dildo.
厚..你要让某位幸运的
Well, you are going to make
流浪妇女爽翻天
Some lucky bag lady very happy.
好吧  我最好还是对你们坦诚
All right, uh, might as well be straight with you.
坦诚  (同"直男")
Straight.
这不是不可能的
It's not impossible, you know.
听着  我知道作为我的朋友
Look, I-I know you guys are my friends,
你们会支持我作出的任何选择
And you'll support me in anything I choose to do.
当然
Of course.
以前你把脚趾甲涂上红色指甲油时
Weren't we there to cheer you on
我们不是在一边欢呼吗
when you painted your toenails magenta?
我决定  我要发掘自己
I've decided that I need to explore
非同志的那一面
the part of me that isn't gay.
哪一面  请你告诉我  哪一面
And what part, pray tell, would that be?
我参加了这个团体  "看见光明"
So, um, I'm, uh... I've joined this group, "See The Light".
该死
Oh, shit.
他们想要帮助我
A-and they're going to help me
找到真实的我
find my way back to my true self.
现在的你  就是真实的你
Who you are is your true self.
不  是我自己放纵才变成这样
No, t-this is who I've allowed myself to become.
胡说八道
That's bullshit!
他们说过你们会这种反应
They said you might react badly.
那帮人还说什麽了
Yeah, what else did they say?
我可以成为上帝希望我成为的那种人
That I could be the person god wants me to be.
老天  艾美特  他们在给你洗脑
Jesus, Emmett, they're brain- washing you.
不  他们没有  他们...
No, they're not. Th-they're...
他们非常...非常友善
they're very... very nice people.
是啊  碰巧这帮人都恨不得
Yeah, who just happen to want every
世上的同志都绝迹
gay person on earth annihilated.
他们还没给你杯「酷爱」有吗   (饮料 暗指洗脑)
They haven't offered you any Kool-Aid yet, have they?
知道吗  我真的不喜欢被嘲笑
You know, I really don't appreciate being mocked.
那是Liza为你亲笔签名的纸巾
That's the napkin that Liza autographed to you.
要丢了
Gone.
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
是我求他陪我一起做HIV筛检的
I'm the one who begged him to come with me for my HIV test.
要不是他自己心中有鬼  也不会发生这些
If he hadn't had that scare, this never would have happened.
他自己失去理智不是你的错
You're not responsible for him losing his mind.
也许他需要的是大干一场
Maybe all he needs is one good fuck
然後就会忘掉这些
And he'll forget all about this.
看这个
Look at this.
巨炮扎克要登台表演
Zack O'Tool is in a play.
那个Ｇ星？
The porn star?
我有他的全系列的DVD
I have his entire oeuvreon dvd.
我都不知道他还会说话
I didn't know he could talk.
好奇这是什麽样的表演
I wonder what kind of play it is.
你认为叫「12个饥渴男人」
Well what kind of play do you think something
还能是什麽表演？
Called "Twelve Horny Men" is?
看一下就知道了
Why don't we find out?
感觉太棒了
That feels so good.
有时候  我可以做任何事
There are times I would do anything
只为能抽根烟
For a cigarette.
那太好了
Well, that's good to know.
那你想抽烟时
So, why don't you indulge yourself
为何不放纵下自己
When you feel like it?
她怀孕後我就戒烟了
Ah, I gave up smoking when the baby came.
琳赛担心吸到二手烟
Lindsay was concerned about second-hand smoke and...
-她是对的  　　 -琳赛是不是那种
-She's right.　 -Is Lindsay one of these people
永远都是对的人？
Who is always infuriatingly right?
几乎所有事情  真该死
About almost everything, damn her.
有你在就轻松多了
It's just that you were such a relief,
我是说那天的送礼会
I mean, at the shower
所有人张口闭口都在谈论孩子
Everyone talking babies, breathing babies.
没错  是有点压抑
Yes, it was a bit oppressive.
别误会  我爱我儿子
I mean, don't get me wrong. I love my son.
-但有时候  　　　　-有时候
-But sometimes...  -Sometimes,
确实需要其他调剂一下
You just need something else.
介意我再抽一支吗
Do you mind if I bum another?
整包都给你了
Have the whole pack.
不  不用了  一支够了
No, that's okay, one'll do.
谢谢
Thank you.
-MM　[机身的刻字]  -对
-"M.M."?　　　　　 -Yeah.
你  我  还有Marilyn Monroe
You, me and Marilyn Monroe.
我们名字缩写都一样
We all have the same initials.
你觉得这代表着什麽
So, what do you think it means?
老天  我们三个中就有两个是拉拉
Jesus, that two out of three of us are dykes.
知道吗  事实上我还听说...
You know, I actually heard...
-不  别说了  老天  -我认真的
-no, stop. oh god! -I'm serious.
我觉得这就是缘份
Well, I think that this is fate.
需要人倾诉的话
Just when you needed someone
我随时奉陪
To tell your troubles to.
倒不是要一五一十地告诉我
Not that you have to tell me,
把我当成你新的挚友
Considering I am your new best friend
为你分担烦恼
And weed pusher.
每个人都有自己的...
Look, everyone has their, uh...
我知道
Yeah, I know.
别急我也会有一堆抱怨的
And wait till you get a load of mine.
但我希望你知道
But I want you to know something.
现下说的每一句话
That whatever's said here at this table
就你我两人知道
Doesn't go any further.
以女童军荣誉做担保
Girl scout's honour.
你认识我多久?
How long have you known me?
我从不跟人约会
I don't do dates.
这不是约会
It's not a date.
我只想知道  你想不想和我一起去巴比伦
I just want to know if you want to come to Babylon with me.
答案是"不"
The answer's no.
我有工作要做
I have work to do.
你何时开始为工作放弃享乐?
Since when has that ever stopped you?
我以为你在准备SATS   (美国的大学指考)
I thought you were studying for your S.A.T.S.
跳舞帮助我集中注意力
Dancing helps me concentrate.
真的
Seriously.
它有助於释放安多酚(内分泌)
Hey, it releases certain endorphins
那样我学习就能...
so that I can study...
更专心  更持久
harder and for longer periods of time.
这麽说来  巴比伦对你健康有益
Hmm, so Babylon is good for your health.
是啊  我头一次听说
Yeah, that's a new one.
我来
I'll get it.
我自己来
谁
Yeah?
我是基普
Hey, it's Kip.
-谁    -不关你的事
-Who?  -It's none of your business.
-基普  -真的是公事
-Kip?  -And it is business,
信不信由你
Believe it or not.
我还是找别人一起跳舞好了
I guess I'll just have to find someone else to dance with.
我也不愁找不到人
It shouldn't be a problem.
然後你学习就能...
And then you can study...
更持久更专心  (双关:又长又硬)
longer and harder.
嗨
Hey.
这里难找吗?
You have any trouble finding it?
不  你指示的方向很清楚
No, your directions were perfect.
很好  你把文件都带来了
Good, you brought your work.
这里真赞
Man, this is awesome.
喝点什麽?
Would you like something to drink?
-有啤酒吗?             -有
-Yeah, you got a beer? -Yeah.
想问一下  希望你不介意
So, if you don't mind my asking,
住这样的地方要多少钱?
How much does a place like this cost?
以你现在的薪水肯定付不起
More than you can afford on your current salary.
这不会太久
Yeah, but not for long.
好了
Yeah.
我相信你会有所成就
I'm sure you're going to go far.
介意我参观一下吗?
You mind if I take a look around?
请便
Go ahead.
我马上过来
I'll be right with you.
好了
So...
我们干嘛不
Why don't we, uh...
准备
Get...
开始
Started?
我也这麽想
That's just what I had in mind.
我们已经被关在这审判室整整3天
We've been locked in this jury room for three days.
整整3天  一直试图做出裁决
Three days trying to reach a verdict.
整整3天  一直与外界隔绝
Three days with no human contact.
整整3天  呼吸这里的空气
Three days breathing the air in here,
充斥着男人的体臭
Thick with the smell of man-stench.
说到体臭
Speaking of stench,
你听过那个桥段没?
You ever heard such dialogue?
闭嘴  太精彩了
Shh, it's brilliant.
现在  只有一个办法打破僵局
Well, there's only one way to break this deadlock.
OJ辛普森案的裁决一定就是这样做出的
This must be how they reached the verdict in the O.J. trial.
我心目中「悬而未决的陪审团」(亦指悬着大屌)
That's what I call a hung jury.
太棒了
Bravo!
刚刚真是一场非常有趣的表演
Uh... uh... that was a very interesting play.
我认为这是对司法体系
To me it challenges the very nature
本质的深层质疑
of our legal system and asks,
「真有可能获得公正的裁决吗?」
"Is it in fact possible to receive a fair trial?"
我认为我们的陪审组织 构造完美　(暗喻阴茎)
Oh, I'd say our judicial branch is in fine shape.
需要我帮你们签名吗?
So, would you like me to sign your programmes?
实际上  巨炮先生
Uh, actually, uh, Mr. O'Tool?
不敢相信我在和巨炮扎克说话
I can't believe I'm actually talking to Zack O'Tool.
不知道你是否也行进一些私下的演出
We were wondering if you ever did personal appearances?
我周六要为新片
I'm cutting the ribbon at a new "Bed,
"饭、屌、爱" 剪彩
Bondage and Beyond" on saturday.
不  我们...我们是说...
Uh, no, we... we meant more...
更私人的...演出
Personal... appearances.
你知道  我们的一个好友
You see, a... a... very good friend of ours
他有点怀疑自己
Is having certain doubts about himself
而你正是他非常喜欢的
And since you are his very favourite
最喜欢的Ｇ星
favourite porn star
我们想如果你可以私下...
We thought a visit from you might...
告诉他叫他来看我的表演
Tell him to come see my show.
或者等到下个月
Or wait till next month,
我的莎士比亚处女作　"科里奥兰纳斯"
I'm making my shakespearean debut as "Coriolanus".
可能那时就太晚了
W-well it might be too late by then.
他现在就需要你
He needs you now.
我们付你一千块美金
We'll pay, $1,000.
-你疯了吗?                         -我还没  不过艾美特快疯了
-Are you out Of your fucking mind? -No, but Emmett is.
茉儿
Mel
很抱歉吵醒你了
Sorry to wake you.
你离开时很生气
You left so angry.
现在几点了?
What time is it?
你去哪了?
Where have you been?
没去哪
Nowhere.
出去了
Out.
你不告诉我去哪  甚至连一通电话也不打?
Not to tell me where you're going, or even call?
如果发生了什麽事  我和盖斯需要你怎麽办？
What if some- thing happened to gus and I needed you?
我告诉你我去抽支烟
I told you I went for a cigarette.
整个晚上?
All night?
我不能有点自己自由的时间吗?
Aren't I allowed any time to myself?
你当然可以有
Of course you are.
我只是担心
I was just worried.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
我去客房睡
I'm going to go sleep in the guest room.
天哪
Oh my god!
你是巨炮扎克
You're Zack O'tool.
我在找艾美特·哈尼卡特
I'm looking for Emmett Honeycutt.
这...这不可能发生的
Okay, that... that's impossible.
为什麽不可能呢?
And why is that?
因为你要找我
Because that's me.
我听说你是我的忠实粉丝
Well, I heard you're one of my biggest fans.
我只是想来看看你有..
So I thought I'd stop by and see just...
多忠实
how big.
你全身每一寸肌肉我都了若指掌
I-I know every inch of you.
我是说...
I-I mean...
我意思是...我对你从里到外...
I mean I... I... I know you inside and...
外　　我是说...
Out. uh... I mean...
我能进去吗?
Mind if I come in?
不介意
No. no.
你...随便一点没关系
Make, uh, m-m-make yourself comfortable.
你知道人们总说世界很小
You know how p-people always say how much smaller
可是在现实生活中见到电影明星机会又有多少？
M-movie stars seem when you s-see them in real life?
你...你真的是...你真的是...
Well, you're... you're a-actually...
不是
Not.
实际上  你看来就像你在那部..
In fact, um, you look just like you did in that, uh,
在「宛如马屌」的场景
Scene in... in "Hung... Hung Like a Horse"
你硬上两个直男那片?
Where you rape the two stable boys?
对  那是我最喜欢的一部
Yeah, one of my favourites.
你知道我最喜欢的一部是
Oh, uh, you know what one I-I really like
「外出就餐」的场景
Is that, uh, scene in "Eating Out",
当你强了两个服务生
When you rape the two busboys.
我很好色的
I'm horny.
我需要发泄
I need some release.
天哪
Oh, my god.
这是你在「深入极限」第二集的台词
That is exactly what you say in "Deep End, part 2"
当时你强干了那两个泳池男孩
When you rape the two pool boys.
我因此得了金屌奖
I got the golden dildo for best actor in that one.
我知道
Uh, I know.
而且你是实至名归
And it was so deserved.
艾美特
Emmett...
不如你来跟我的
How'd you like to make friends with my...
小老弟深交一下？
Buddy here.
我?
Me?
给巨炮扎克口交?
Blow Zack O'tool?
我一直幻想这一刻到来
I have dreamt about this moment all my life.
他也期待着你
Well, he's waiting for you.
-怎麽样?               -我正要去开会
-Hey, how's it going?  -I've got a meeting
我20分钟後在办公室外面有个会议
outside the office in 20 minutes
我希望不是像我们在外面开的那种会
I hope it's not like our meeting outside the office.
什麽?
What?
我们什麽时候再见?
So when do you want to get together?
叫辛西娅查一下我的排程
Ask Cynthia to check my schedule,
可能在舒尔曼鞋的会议之後
Maybe after the Schulmann meeting.
我的意思是吃晚饭
I meant for dinner.
我不知道  我快迟到了
I don't know. I'm late.
听着  在你走之前我有些事要说
Listen, before you go, there's something
我想问你
I want to ask you.
你只有30秒
You have 30 seconds.
戴夫·哈考特提升为主管了
Dave Harcourt's being bumped up to director,
这意味着他那个经理的职位空出来了
Which means his manager position's going to be available.
我想得到这个职位
I'd like to go up for it.
而且我希望你能推荐我
And I'd like you to recommend me.
我想我会做好的
I think I'd be damn good.
我想也是
I think you would be, too.
-谢谢     -但不是现在
-Thanks.  -But not yet.
-为什麽不?  -这太快了
-Why not?   -it's too soon.
那为什麽你一直说我的创意很好?
Then why do you keep telling me how great my ideas are?
创意确实是好  但你还有很多要学
They are, but you still have a lot to learn.
我可以边做边学
I can learn on the job.
我欣赏你的野心
I admire your ambition,
可是你需要更多经验
But you need the ex- perience to back it up.
-不要着急       -我没有时间了
-Give it time.  -I don't have time.
到时候他们会把职位给别人的
By then they'll have given it to someone else.
你看  我知道我会很棒的
Look, I know I'd be perfect.
我告诉你
I told you.
你还没有准备好
You're not ready.
又一个男孩
Another boy.
我们这一群人还没有一个生女孩呢
No one in the group's had a girl yet.
我知道有两个人  哈利和萨姆
I know two guys, Harry and Sam,
他们就刚生了一个小女孩
They just had a little girl.
-我是琳赛  　　 -我是玛丽安
-I'm Lindsay.   -Marianne.
送礼会上我有出席
Uh, I was at the shower.
对
That's right.
要知道  你们家真的很漂亮
Yeah. you know, you two really have a beautiful home,
你们还有一个漂亮的儿子
And a beau- tiful son.
你有个完美的生活
Hell, you've got a beautiful life.
我希望你们俩能好好照顾对方
I hope you two take care of each other,
保护你拥有的一切
You know, protect what you've got.
你不会想失去这些的
You don't want to lose it.
弗兰妮和佐伊生了个男孩
Franny and Zoe had a boy.
他取名叫霍顿
His name's Holden.
你来了  茉儿
There you are, Mel.
快来看看我们盖斯新结交的好朋友
Come look at Gus' new best friend.
他太漂亮了
He's, uh, gorgeous.
是不是有种似曾相识的感觉?
It like deja vu?
我的意思是不久之前
I mean, it wasn't that long ago
你和琳赛就在这里
You and Linz were right here.
我记得你们看起来是那麽的喜悦
I remember how radiant you two looked.
你们现在看起来也是那样
You two look the same way.
不好意思我出去一下
Would you guys excuse me?
茉儿?
Mel?
我们当时的确很开心  不是吗?
We were radiant, weren't we?
那时我们在这里  我们有了我们的盖斯
When we were here, when we had Gus,
我们真的很开心
We were so happy.
这是我人生中最美好的时刻
Yeah, it was the most beautiful moment of my life.
是我们俩的生活
Our lives.
可是我们现在为什麽变成这样?
So how did it get to this?
-怎麽了?   -变成现在这样
-To what?  -to where we are.
我们之间存在问题  但是...
We have our problems, but...
不  不只是问题
No, they're just not problems.
所有事情都不对劲
Everything's wrong.
不是每件事
Not everything.
好的  我一直在想
Look, I've been thinking.
如果和其他人聊聊会有些帮助的话
If it would help to talk to someone,
那正是我们所需要的  就像你说的那样
Then that's what we should do, like you said.
发生了一些事情
Something happened.
什麽?
What?
一些事情...
Something...
发生了  不过我并不想这样的
happened. I-I didn't mean for it to...
但确实发生了
But it did.
我不明白  你什麽...
I don't understand. What do you...
你什麽意思?
what do you mean?
你...
You...
那个人是谁
Who was it?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
护士马上要来把婴儿抱走了
The nurse has come to get the baby.
你们只有几分钟的探望时间
You only have a few more minutes.
对不起  琳赛
I'm sorry, Linz.
你叫巨炮扎克去勾引艾美特?
Y-you hooked Emmett up with Zack O'tool?
我真希望我可以在场看看他的表情
I wish I could've been there to see his face
-当他打开门                -看到偶像站在自己面前
-When he opened the door.  -Just saw him standing there.
据说巨炮扎克的阴茎有12英寸长(30公分!!)
Zack O'tool's supposed to have a 12-inch dick.
你又知道巨炮扎克了?
How do you know who Zack O'tool is?
种马巨炮的名号无人不知
Everybody knows who the manrammer is.
就连在学的学生也知道?
Even schoolboys?
当然了  这是必修课程之一
Of course. That's part of the curriculum.
G星小学堂第一课
Gay porn stars 101.
下面我亲自教授第一课
Yeah, and here's the first lesson
有得干的人不用学  有得学的人没得干
Those that can, do, and those that can't watch porn.
待会儿见  孩子们
See ya, boys.
嘿  布莱恩
Hey, Brian.
你想跳舞吗?
You wanna dance?
没兴趣
I don't think so.
现在又不是在办公室   我们一起去跳舞吧
We're not in the office now, let's get down.
我很忙
I'm busy.
至少刚刚还在忙
Or at least I was.
-你嗑了什麽药?    -重剂量可卡因
-What're you on?  -Double bumps.
你不该让我这个上司知道的
You shouldn't let senior management know that.
我只是在庆祝而已
I'm just celebrating.
今晚是个特殊的日子
See, tonight's a special occasion.
-是吗  -是啊  你没听说吗?
-Oh?   -Yeah, you didn't hear?
吉姆·克莱门斯基得到那个职位了
Jim Clemenski got that position.
就是你不肯向高层推荐我去的那个职位
You know the one you... wouldn't recommend me for?
-听着  我告诉过你...  -你欠我的
-Look, I told you...  -You owed it to me.
为什麽  就因为我干过你吗?
Why, because I fucked you?
你那时根本也不厉害
You weren't that good.
我是同志  你也是同志
I'm gay, you're gay.
是啊  我们都是同志
Yeah, we're all gay.
你觉得我就应该欠你一份人情？
Do you think that means I owe you some favour?
如果我们自己都不互相帮助
How else are we supposed to get ahead
怎麽能提高同志在社会中的地位?
if we don't help each other?
像我一样  自己努力
The same way that I did. By helping yourself.
还有  工作表现比其他人都出色
Yeah, and by doing your job better than anyone else.
如果你可以做到这些  相信我
If you can do that, then trust me,
他们不会管你干的是男人还是女人
They won't give a shit where you stick your dick.
还有不要酒和毒品混着吃
And don't mix that with booze.
看到没  就是我的特别关照
There. I did you a favour.
你到底死去哪?  回我电话
Where the hell are you? Call me.
这是我第四次留言给他了
That's the fourth message I've left for him.
他可能被巨炮扎克操翻了
He's probably still recovering
还在恢复当中
From having Zack O'Tool fuck his brains out.
如果这可以让他
If that's what it takes for him
不再相信什麽"迎向光明"之类的鬼话
Never to think of "See the Light" again,
那我的一千大洋也就值得了
Then that $1,000 dollars I spent was well worth it.
我的老天爷
Oh, god.
看  他在那  小艾  艾美特
Oh, there he is! Em, Emmett!
艾美特
Emmett!
你跑去哪了?
Where have you been?
你没听我们的留言吗?
Did you get our messages?
我最近很忙
Uh, I've been busy.
我想也是
I'll bet you have.
去跟我们一起喝一杯吧
So, come have a drink with us.
我  我  不行  我要去见一个人
Uh, I-I can't, I'm... I'm meeting someone.
一个男人吗?
A guy?
如果你们非要知道的话  是的
If you must know, yes.
他的名字叫马特
His name's Matt.
根据我的统计  叫马特的男人87.5%都很可爱
Guys named matt are, by my calculation, 87.5% cute.
看来那方法的确奏效了
It must have worked.
那麽  快跟我们说说吧
So, tell us all about it.
说什麽?
All about what?
那天晚上的事
The other night.
哪天晚上?
The other night?
你知道  某个神秘人物
You know, when a certain someone
挺着装备精良的「重量级巨炮」
With a well-endowed something
过去咚咚地敲开了你的菊花门
Came a tap-tap- tapping at your chamber door.
噢  你是说扎克
Oh, you mean Zack.
「你是说扎克」　听听   他讲得多轻描淡写
"Oh, you mean Zack." I love how he's so blase about it.
那的确让我大开眼界
It was quite an eye-opening experience.
我非常感激你
And I owe it all to you.
为朋友我可以赴汤蹈火
Oh, anything for a friend.
只要能奏效
Just as long as it did the trick.
确实很有效
It did the trick, all right.
我  我都不知道该怎麽感谢你才好
I-I... really I can't thank you enough.
那天让我证明了
It helped me prove to myself that, uh,
我可以抵抗任何诱惑
I can resist any temptation,
哪怕面对这个唯一
Even the only man
让我可以光靠意淫就能高潮的男人
I've ever had a spontaneous orgasm over...
也同时证明了我卓越的意志力
Provided my resolve is strong enough.
什麽?
What?
你是说那天你们什麽也没做吗?
You mean you didn't do anything?
-我们聊天了呀  -就光聊天?
-Talked.       -You talked?
你知道他的老师是乌塔·哈根吗?
Did you know that he studied acting with Uta Hagen,
他可以流利地说三国语言
And he's fluent in three languages?
我付他一千美金是去帮你润菊　可不是陪你聊天的
Yeah, that's not the kind of tongue action I paid $1,000 for.
你花了一千美金?
You paid $1,000?
你他妈的说对了  老兄
You're damn right I did, buddy.
他们说你会不择手段地
Wow, they told me you would stop at nothing
以防我找到真正的我
To prevent me from finding my true self,
看来他们说对了
And they were right.
艾美特  听我说
Emmett, listen to me.
你已经找到真实的自我了
You've already found your true self.
你真实的自我就是个超级C妹娘娘
Your true self is a big, nelly queen
天生就爱跪在地上替男人吸舔大屌
Who likes to get down on his knees and suck cock,
有一年万圣节
And once a year on Halloween
你扮成这世上有史以来
Dress up as the ugliest fucking Cher
最丑爆的雪儿
That the world has ever seen.
这都还没什麽
And that's okay.
你应该赶快远离那些乱七八糟的人
Now you've got to get away from those sicko creeps
以免他们把你给毁了
Before they destroy you.
不  不  实际上
No. no, actually
我应该远离你们
It's you I h-have to get away from.
他们努力让我明白这一点
Uh, they tried to tell me that,
只是我不肯相信他们
Only I didn't want to believe them.
现在我终於看见那道光了
But now I see the light.
茉儿?
Mel?
你不必离开的
You don't have to go.
我已经带给了你太多的伤害
I've caused enough harm.
如果我不走  只会毁了你  我  还有盖斯
It would only be destructive to you, to me, to Gus.
你还没告诉我你要去哪儿
You haven't even told me where you're going.
去她那里?
To her?
我和她之间从没认真过的
There was never any intention of it,
我们根本就没有想过要进一步发展
On either of our parts, to be anything more than what it was.
我要去我表姐丽塔那
I'm going to go stay at my cousin Rita's.
就是那个说我们俩永远不会在一起的人吗?
The one with the overbite who never thought we'd make it?
天啊
God.
我想她应该很高兴自己成功预言了
Well, I think she deserves the prize for being right, huh?
我想我没什麽好说的
Well, I guess that's everything for now.
我可以和盖斯独处一会儿吗?
Can I have a moment alone with Gus?
我们认为这些50年代的怀旧元素
We thought the nostalgic reference to the '50s
会让那些用假牙的人产生共鸣
Would appeal to the denture set.
提醒他们美好年华已逝吗?
By reminding them that their best years are behind them?
而他们的未来
And that all they have to look forward to
只会更加糟糕
Is further deterioration
还要面临死亡
And death.
我们认为这会让他们会心一笑
W-we thought it would make them smile.
他们才不敢张嘴大笑
They're afraid to smile.
因为怕他们恶心的假牙会掉下来
Their fucking teeth will fall out.
基普去哪了?
Where's Kip?
他打电话来说生病了
Uh, he called in sick.
见鬼
Shit.
布莱恩  我能跟你谈谈吗?
Brian, can I talk with you?
我晚点再来找你们算账
I'll finish berating you later.
-什麽事?　　　-该你来告诉我
-What's up?   -You tell me.
法务部刚刚收到基普·汤玛斯的律师发来的传真
Legal just received this fax from Kip Thomas' lawyer.
他说你曾答应帮助汤玛斯的事业
He says that you promised to help Mr. Thomas' career
但必须用性服务来交换
In exchange for sexual favours
当他完成性服务以後
And that when he, um, complied,
你却违背承诺
You rescinded your offer.
简直是彻头彻尾的胡说八道
Well, that's complete and utter bullshit.
不管是不是胡说八道  反正他准备提告
Well, bullshit or not, he is suing you...
还有公司
and us,
罪名是性骚扰
for sexual harassment.
6f4acbeb15f44a7fb93620b68db9bc26